Center for a Woman's Own Name Records
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- State File, 1969-1985 (Box 3-12)
  - General (Box 3)
    - New Mexico (Box 8)
      - Attorney general, 1983 (Box 8)
      - Individuals, Joiner, Carol, 1972-1976 (Box 8)
    - New York (Box 8)
      - Attorney general, 1983 (Box 8)
      - General correspondence (Box 8)
        - 1973-1975 (Box 8)
        - 1976-1984 (Box 8)
      - Individuals (Box 8)
        - Burrell, Jane E., 1973-1974 (Box 8)
        - Carlsson, Kathleen A. Ryan, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
        - Cohen, Marsha, 1974 (Box 8)
        - Vanderbilt, Amy, 1973-1974 (Box 8)
      - Legislative file, 1983 (Box 8)
      - Organizations and schools, 1974-1975, 1981 (Box 8)
      - Press, 1980-1984 (Box 8)
    - North Carolina (Box 8)
      - Attorney general, 1974 (Box 8)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box 8)
      - Legislative file, 1983 (Box 8)
    - North Dakota (Box 8)
      - Attorney general, 1983 (Box 8)
      - General correspondence, 1978-1981 (Box 8)
      - Legislative file, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Ohio (Box 8)
      - Attorney general, 1973, 1983 (Box 8)
      - General correspondence (Box 8)
        - 1973-1976 (Box 8)
        - 1977-1983 (Box 8)
      - Individuals (Box 8)
        - Luggen, James Anthony, 1974 (Box 8)
        - Various, 1974 (Box 8)
      - Legislative file, 1979, 1983 (Box 8)
    - Oklahoma (Box 8)
      - Attorney general, 1983 (Box 8)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box 8)
      - Legislative file, 1981-1982 (Box 8)
    - Oregon (Box 8)
      - General correspondence, 1974-1983 (Box 8)
      - Legislative file, 1982 (Box 8)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 9)
      - Attorney general, 1973, 1983 (Box 9)
      - Attorneys, Morrison, David Rittenhouse, 1973 (Box 9)
      - General correspondence (Box 9)
        - 1973 (Box 9)
        - 1974-1983 (Box 9)
      - Individuals (Box 9)
        - Campana, Georgia F., 1973 (Box 9)
        - Ravinsky-Fleeger, Annette, 1983-1984 (Box 9)
        - Various, 1973-1974 (Box 9)
      - Legislative file, 1974-1983 (Box 9)
      - Organizations and schools, 1973-1974, 1981-1982 (Box 9)
      - Press, 1973-1984 (Box 9)
    - Rhode Island (Box 9)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1982 (Box 9)
      - Legislative file, 1983 (Box 9)
      - Litigation, Kathryn M. Traugott v. Eugene Petit, Registrar, 1979 (Box 9)
    - South Carolina (Box 9)
      - General correspondence, 1980-1983 (Box 9)
      - Legislative file, 1976, 1983 (Box 9)
      - Subject file, children's names, 1980 (Box 9)
    - South Dakota (Box 9)
      - General correspondence, 1980 (Box 9)
      - Legislative file, 1982 (Box 9)
    - Tennessee (Box 9)
      - Attorney general, 1983 (Box 9)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box 9)
      - Individuals (Box 9)
        - Camp, Mary Jo Bruce, 1974, 1980 (Box 9)
        - Woods, Jayne O., 1973-1974 (Box 9)
    - Texas (Box 9)
      - Attorney general, 1973-1974 (Box 9)
      - General correspondence (Box 9)
        - 1973-1978 (Box 9)
        - 1980-1983 (Box 9)
      - Individuals (Box 9)
        - Duplechin, Ida Lee, 1974-1978 (Box 9)
        - Hunter, Marsha, 1974-1976 (Box 9)
        - Morales, Catherine, 1973 (Box 9)
        - Neal, Bobbie Gaylenn, 1973-1974 (Box 9)
        - Sheley, Kathy Ann, 1973 See also Container 1, Correspondence, Federal government, Navy (Box 9)
      - Legislative file, 1973-1974, 1983 (Box 9)
      - Organizations and schools, 1973-1982 (Box 9)
      - Press, 1976-1982 (Box 9)
      - Subject file, driver's licenses, 1973 (Box 9)
    - Utah, General correspondence, 1974, 1984 (Box 10)
    - Vermont (Box 10)
      - Attorney general, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1976, 1982 (Box 10)
    - Virginia (Box 10)
      - Attorneys, 1973-1974, 1982 (Box 10)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box 10)
      - Organizations and schools, 1974, 1980 (Box 10)
      - Press, 1980-1985 (Box 10)
    - Washington (Box 10)
      - Attorney general, 1973 (Box 10)
      - Attorneys, 1974 (Box 10)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1983 (Box 10)
    - West Virginia (Box 10)
      - Attorney general, 1975 (Box 10)
      - General correspondence, 1973-1985 (Box 10)
      - Subject file, children's names, 1973-1975 (Box 10)
    - Wisconsin (Box 10)
      - Attorney general, 1973 (Box 10)
      - Attorneys, 1974 (Box 10)
      - General correspondence, 1974-1983 (Box 10)
      - Harney, Kathleen R., 1973-1974 See also Container 12, State File, Volunteers, Wisconsin, Kessler, Joan (Box 10)
      - Organizations and schools, 1974-1982 See also Container 12, State File, Volunteers, Wisconsin, Olympia Brown League (Box 10)
  - Volunteers (Box 10)
    - Alabama, Knowles, Ralph I., 1972-1974 (Box 10)
    - Alaska, Derderian, Lynn A., 1973-1974 (Box 10)
    - Arizona (Box 10)
      - Freund, Susan, 1973-1975 (Box 10)
      - Various, 1973-1978 (Box 10)
    - Arkansas (Box 10)
      - Various, 1973-1978 (Box 10)
      - Walker, Pamela, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
    - California (Box 10)
      - Blumenberg, Susan, 1973-1975 (Box 10)
      - Fisher, Mary-Lynn, 1973-1975 (Box 10)
      - Goins, Neva, 1974-1975 (Box 10)
      - Lane, Lucia, 1974 (Box 10)
      - Montandon, Pat, 1973-1974 See also Container 2, Correspondence, Individuals, MacDougall, Priscilla Ruth with Terri P. Tepper (Box 10)
      - Press, 1974, undated (Box 10)
      - Slocum, Robert, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - Stannard, Una, 1973-1974 See also Container 17, Miscellany, Promotional materials, publications, and other writings, Other (Box 10)
      - Various, 1973-1974 (Box 10)
      - Women's History Research Center, Berkeley, California, 1973-1976 (Box 10)
    - Colorado (Box 11)
      - Ohneck, Lyndy, 1973 (Box 11)
      - Various, 1973-1977 (Box 11)
    - Connecticut (Box 11)
      - Various, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Wright, Pamela, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
    - Delaware (Box 11)
      - Dever, Priscilla E., 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Stuber, Gloria, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Various, 1973-1975 (Box 11)
    - District of Columbia (Box 11)
      - Fuller, Mary, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Individuals, 1973-1978 (Box 11)
      - Organizations and schools, 1975-1979 (Box 11)
      - Sandler, Bernice, 1974-1976 (Box 11)
    - Florida (Box 11)
      - Dore, Patricia, 1973 (Box 11)
      - Parson, Stewart E., 1973-1976 (Box 11)
      - Wilson, Judy, 1974-1976 (Box 11)
    - Hawaii, Various, 1976 (Box 11)
    - Idaho, Strahman, Myrna, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
    - Illinois, Allen, Barbara J., 1974 (Box 11)
    - Maine, Matthews, Kim, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
    - Michigan, King, Jean L., 1984 (Box 11)
    - Missippippi, Muirhead, Jean D., 1974 (Box 11)
    - New York (Box 11)
      - 1974-1981 (Box 11)
      - 1982 (Box 11)
      - 1983-1989 (Box 11)
    - Ohio, Markunas, Patricia V., 1973-1974 (Box 11)
    - Oregon, 1973-1980 (Box 11)
    - Pennsylvania (Box 11)
      - Baseman, Debbie, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Smales, Sandra, 1974 (Box 11)
      - Stark, Caryn L., 1973 (Box 11)
      - Women's Law Project, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
    - Rhode Island (Box 11)
      - Sousa, Sheila Cabral, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Various, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
    - South Carolina, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
    - South Dakota, 1973-1977 (Box 11)
    - Tennessee (Box 11)
      - Brookman, Rosemary, 1973 (Box 11)
      - Various, 1973-1977 (Box 11)
    - Texas (Box 11)
      - Duplechin, Ida Lee, 1973-1977 (Box 11)
      - Various, 1973-1974 (Box 11)
      - Weddington, Sarah Ragle, 1973-1974 See also Container 17, Miscellany, Promotional materials, publications, and other writings, Other (Box 11)
    - Utah (Box 12)
      - Greenwold, Marcia, 1973 (Box 12)
      - Tyler, Jan, 1972-1973 (Box 12)
      - Various, 1973, 1979 (Box 12)
    - Vermont, 1973 (Box 12)
    - Virginia, Heinz, Elise B., 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - Washington (Box 12)
      - Conrad-Rice, Joy Belle, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
      - Hankamer, Mary, 1973-1974 See also Container 1, Correspondence, Foreign file, Morocco (Box 12)
      - Spitzer, Hugh D., 1973-1976 See also Container 17, Miscellany, Promotional materials, publications, and other writings, Academic papers, 1972-1973 (Box 12)
    - West Virginia, Falk, Gail, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - Wisconsin (Box 12)
      - Kessler, Joan F., 1973-1974 See also Container 10, State File, Wisconsin, Harney, Kathleen R. (Box 12)
      - Olympia Brown League, 1974-1978 See also Container 10, State File, Wisconsin, Organizations and schools (Box 12)
      - Various, 1973-1974 (Box 12)
    - Wyoming, 1973-1976 (Box 12)
- Consumer Credit Project, 1973-1984 (Box 12-14)
  Correspondence, clippings, legal files, promotional materials, publications, and surveys.
  Arranged alphabetically by topic and type of material and chronologically therein.
  - Administrative file (Box 12)
    - Agendas, minutes, and reports, 1976-1979 (Box 12)
    - Credit survey, 1975-1977 See also Container 14, Miscellany, Administrative file, Credit survey (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous notes, undated (Box 12)
    - Planning and strategies, 1976-1978 (Box 12)
  - Clippings (Box 12)
    - Magazine and journal articles, 1974-1981, undated (Box 12)
    - Newsletters and press releases, other, 1974-1981 (Box 12)
    - Newspaper articles (Box 12)
      - 1974, June-1975, Apr. (Box 12)
      - 1975, May (Box 12)
      - 1975, June-Dec. (Box 12)
      - 1976 (Box 12)
      - 1977-1983, undated (Box 12)
    - Press, 1976-1983, undated (Box 12)
    - Correspondence (Box 13)
      - Board of Directors, 1976-1978 (Box 13)
      - Federal agencies and departments, 1976-1981 (Box 13)
      - General, 1975-1979 (Box 13)
      - Individuals, Groupe, Leonard M. and others, 1977-1981 (Box 13)
      - Organizations and schools, 1976-1981 (Box 13)
      - Press (Box 13)
        - Print (Box 13)
          - 1973-1979 (Box 13)
          - 1980-1983, undated (Box 13)
        - Radio and television, 1975-1982 (Box 13)
        - Response to advertisements and articles (Box 13)
          - 1974-1978, undated (Box 13)
          - 1979 (Box 13)
          - 1980-1984 (Box 13)
      - Quotable letters, 1977-1983 (Box 13)
      - State government (Box 13)
        - Illinois, 1975-1976 (Box 13)
        - Various, 1974-1980 (Box 13)
    - Credit discrimination complaints (Box 13)
      - Credit card companies, 1974-1980 (Box 13)
      - Gas companies, 1975-1980 (Box 13)
      - General public, 1976-1982 (Box 13)
      - J.C. Penney Co., 1977-1981 (Box 14)
      - Military personnel, 1977-1979 (Box 14)
      - Resolved, 1977-1978 (Box 14)
    - Legal file, 1976, undated (Box 14)
    - Promotional materials, publications, and other writings (Box 14)
      - New Credit Rights for Women, Barrington, Ill.: Consumer Credit Project, 1978 (Box 14)
        - Booklet, 1978, undated (Box 14)
        - Research articles, 1974-1975, undated (Box 14)
        - Teaching guide, 1977-1979 (Box 14)
      - Pamphlets, others, 1975-1977, undated (Box 14)
- Miscellany, 1956-2008 (Box 14-17)
  Administrative files, announcements, clippings, legal files, promotional materials, publications, scrapbook, and writings.
  Arranged alphabetically by type of material and chronologically therein.
  - Administrative file (Box 14)
    - Bills, 1973-1979 (Box 14)
    - Budget proposals, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
    - By-laws, 1974 (Box 14)
    - Credit survey, 1975-1976 See also Container 12, Consumer Credit Project, Administrative file, Credit survey (Box 14)
    - Financial records, 1974-1979 (Box 14)
    - Fundraising, 1974-1975 (Box 14)
    - Historical file (Box 14)
      - Center for a Woman's Own Name, 1972-1980, 2008 (Box 14)
      - Lucy Stone League, 1956, Undated (Box 14)
    - Questionnaire, 1975-1976 (Box 14)
  - Announcements (Box 15)
    - A-B, 1975-1983, undated (Box 15)
    - C-E, 1975-1983, undated (Box 15)
    - F-H, 1975-1983, undated (Box 15)
    - I-M, 1975-1984, undated (Box 15)
    - N-R, 1975-1983, undated (Box 15)
    - S-T, 1974-1982, undated (Box 15)
    - V-Z, 1974-1982, undated (Box 15)
  - Clippings (Box 15)
    - Articles (Box 15)
      - 1971-1973 (Box 15)
      - 1974-1975 (Box 15)
      - 1976 (Box 15)
      - 1977-1986 (Box 15)
      - undated (Box 15)
    - Federal regulations, 1975 (Box 15)
    - Press, 1973-2008 (Box 15)
  - Legal file (Box 16)
    - Articles of Incorporation, 1973-1974 (Box 16)
    - United States Internal Revenue Service, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
    - Weiner work file (Box 16)
      - Cases (Box 16)
        - Tepper, Terri P., drafts, 1972, undated (Box 16)
        - Various, 1972, undated (Box 16)
      - Correspondence, 1972-1975 (Box 16)
      - Opinions, 1972-1974 (Box 16)
      - Research (Box 16)
        - Articles, 1972-1973, undated (Box 16)
        - Case law, Undated, (2 folders) (Box 16)
      - Wangerin, Reet (Box 16)
        - Case file, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
        - Correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 16)
        - Drafts, 1974 (Box 16)
        - Research, 1974, undated (Box 16)
  - Promotional materials, publications, and other writings (Box 17)
    - Academic papers (Box 17)
      - 1972-1973 See also Container 12, State File, Volunteers, Washington, Spitzer, Hugh D. (Box 17)
      - Undated (Box 17)
    - Booklets, Center for a Woman's Own Name, 1974-1975 (Box 17)
    - Cartoons (Box 17)
      - Center for a Woman's Own Name, 1974 (Box 17)
      - Other, 1977, undated (Box 17)
    - Fact sheets, 1973, undated (Box 17)
    - Forms, undated (Box 17)
    - MacDougall, Priscilla Ruth, 1972-1979 (Box 17)
    - Newsletters and press releases (Box 17)
      - Center for a Woman's Own Name, 1974 (Box 17)
      - Other, 1970, 1976-1978, undated (Box 17)
    - Other, 1973-1975, 1981 See also Container 10, State File, Volunteers, California, Stannard, Una See also Container 11, State File, Volunteers, Texas, Weddington, Sarah Ragle (Box 17)
    - Women and law, 1971-1975 (Box 18)
  - Scrapbook (Box 18)
    - 1973-1974, undated, (2 folders) (Box 18)